[
    {
      "question": "What is the one place you cannot apparate at?",
      "choice1": "Hogsmeade",
      "choice2": "Grimauld's Palace",
      "choice3": "Azkaban",
      "choice4": "Hogwarts",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question":
        "Who smashes the knot on the whomping willow that leads to a secret passageway?",
      "choice1": "Harry",
      "choice2": "Remus",
      "choice3": "Crookshanks",
      "choice4": "Padfoot",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question":
        "Which of these Dumbledoor's office passwords does Harry accidently guess?",
      "choice1": "Sherbet Lemon",
      "choice2": "Cockroach cluster",
      "choice3": "Fizzing Whizbee ",
      "choice4": "Acid pops",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question":
        "What does Romilda Vane spike with a love potion?",
      "choice1": "Chocolate Cauldrons",
      "choice2": "Butterbeer",
      "choice3": "Pudding",
      "choice4": "Pumpkin Juice",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who gets Harry Potter Gillyweed?",
      "choice1": "Sirius Black",
      "choice2": "Neville Longbottom",
      "choice3": "Dobby the house elf",
      "choice4": "Professor Moody",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Where does Rita Skeeter get her information on Dumbledore?",
      "choice1": "Aunt Muriel",
      "choice2": "Bathilda Bagshot",
      "choice3": "Hermione Granger",
      "choice4": "Snape",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who sends Aunt Petunia the Howler's?",
      "choice1": "Prof. Snape",
      "choice2": "Dumbledore",
      "choice3": "Molly Weasley",
      "choice4": "Mad Eye Moody",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among the following wizards does winky despise?",
      "choice1": "Harry Potter",
      "choice2": "Albus Dumbledore",
      "choice3": "Ludo Bagman",
      "choice4": "Barty Crouch Jr.",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Ariana Dumbledore rumored to be?",
      "choice1": "A squib",
      "choice2": "A murderer",
      "choice3": "A wizard",
      "choice4": "An Obscurial",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Dumbledore rumoured to be in love with?",
      "choice1": "Grindelwald",
      "choice2": "Bathilda Bagshot",
      "choice3": "Gregorovitch",
      "choice4": "Snape",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who did Aunt Muriel say looked like an `omelette`?",
      "choice1": "Fred Weasly",
      "choice2": "Bathilda Bagshot",
      "choice3": "Xenophilius Lovegood",
      "choice4": "Ronald",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Whose death does Professor Trelawney correctly predict at the Christmas dinner?",
      "choice1": "Harry Potter",
      "choice2": "Dumbledore",
      "choice3": "Peter Pettigrew",
      "choice4": "Minerva McGonagall",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What house is Nymphadora tonks in?",
      "choice1": "Gryffindor",
      "choice2": "Hufflepuff",
      "choice3": "Ravenclaw",
      "choice4": "Slytherin",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What Animagus can Rita Skater transform into?",
      "choice1": "A dog",
      "choice2": "A mosquito",
      "choice3": "A water beetle",
      "choice4": "A frog",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Where can Voldemort not harm Harry Potter?",
      "choice1": "The Dursleys",
      "choice2": "Hogsmeade",
      "choice3": "Diagon Alley",
      "choice4": "London",
      "answer": 1
    }
    
  
  ]
